#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/henry-asmar-04a462150 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word

### Certifications

Battle of The Bands 2011 Business Basic Training

# Henry Asmar

Customer Care Consultant at Maxis Selangor

### Summary

Highly results-oriented individual with over 4 years experience as a role in customer service and it's driven me to carry this as a career due to passion and enthusiasm to diligently deliver the excellent service as well practicing critical thinking that would be the factor to executing perfect solution to meet customer or consumer needs and requirements in order to sustain a trust of customer or client on the particular brand.

## Experience

Maxis Business
Customer Care Consultant
February 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

#### Hilton

Call Center Agent July 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 7 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Handling and manage all amenities that related with guest tiers and event. Also handling closing for in-room dine cashier before it will send over to finance. And for the last but not least that really high important is to perfectly allies will respective department and accurate instruction to fulfill and deliver all guest needs and provide all answer and solution according to international 5 star hotel standard in order to carry sustainability and improvise on guest accommodation experience.

Rio Kiara Sdn Bhd Customer Service Professional (Ultra Mobile) May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month) Taman Tun Dr Ismail

"#Handle all of the inquires, payment, complaint, billing issue, refund request and network issue and perform the troubleshoot with Ultra Mobile customers from North America.

"#Escalate the issue and follow up if necessary for certain cases such as network issue, refund request and order status.

United Overseas Bank Limited (UOB)
Customer Service Officer
October 2016 - May 2017 (8 months)
Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- "#Comply and maintaining service standard as a Bank to respond the inquiries pertaining to credit card services.
- <sup>a</sup>#Handled customer complaints with correct judgment and critical thinking to resolve issues.
- <sup>o</sup>#Ensure all customer request and follow-up done smoothly and well delivered according SLA to meet customer expectation.
- "#Acknowledge for all on-going promotion and escalate case with complete report before route to the respective department.

IOI Corporation Berhad Customer Service Officer (IOI City Mall) November 2015 - August 2016 (10 months) Putra Jaya, Malaysia

- <sup>a</sup>#Handle inquiries and complain from tenants and customers, and provide hospitality and facility to customers.
- "#Frequently liaise with other department such as Housekeeping, Building Service, Auxiliary Police, Advertising & Promotion, Leasing & Marketing department.
- <sup>a</sup>#Send and receive the update regarding Technical issue, Cleanliness, Awareness, Accident and Incident, and as well with upcoming or ongoing event and promotion.

HSBC Electronics Data Processing (M) Sdn. Bhd Global Support Executive February 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 3 months) Cyberjaya, Malaysia

- "#Handled and processed offshore banking application form received from Customers all over 140+ countries that we served, which are then scanned into the system and ensure all criteria are fulfilled and meet all risk and compliance requirements before opening of an account.
- <sup>a</sup>#We handled all requests from new account, amended or updated customer records.
- <sup>a</sup>#Taxation, refunds, validation, internal, internet, outward payment and etc. are part of my responsibilities.

Digi Telecommunications
Customer Services Representative
January 2009 - January 2010 (1 year 1 month)
Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- "#Facing customer in person and handle customer inquiry about the plan or package, bill payment, billing issue, technical issue and complain.
- <sup>a</sup>#Provide the best solution when needed and necessary.

#### **VADS** Berhad

Tele-Marketer

August 2008 - January 2009 (6 months)

Taman Tun Dr Ismail

<sup>a</sup>#Required to sell and explain the latest product which called SME Wang that launched by TM (Telekom Malaysia) to all SME in Malaysia.

### Education

S.M.K Cheras Jaya

Business/Commerce, General · (2000 - 2005)